http://www.american-iranian.org/privacy-policy

About/HistoryMission & VisionFAQMedia Kit
Research/BooksPublicationsMyth vs. FactIndustry SpotlightMedia Guides
About/HistoryMission & VisionFAQMedia Kit
Research/BooksPublicationsMyth vs. FactIndustry SpotlightMedia Guides
Privacy Policy
The American Iranian Council (AIC) is committed to protecting the privacy of its visitors, members and donors online.AIC makes every effort to ensure that all the communications and transactions that occur on its website are secure. AIC does not share any financial information provided during donation on the site to third parties. AIC secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. Credit card information is not stored permanently on the Web server. AIC does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.AIC Email PolicyAIC sends its members and subscribers regular newsletters on latest events, updates and news. If you do not wish to receive AIC newsletters, you may opt out when you receive the next issue by clicking the “unsubscribe” button. If you wish to be removed from our mailing list altogether, please e-mail: info@american-iranian.orgAIC Copyright and Trademark NoticesAll contents of the American Iranian Council Web Site are Copyright © 2011 All rights reserved. However, you are free to view, copy, print, distribute, and post AIC material from this site, as long as:The material is used for non-commercial purposes.The contents are not misrepresented.All copyright notices are affixed to the material and the following copyright notice appear on each document: "Copyright © 2011 AIC. All Rights Reserved."Contact InformationAmerican Iranian Council welcomes your comments and any concerns you may have in regards to our website. If you require any further information or clarification, please do not hesitate to contact us at: info@american-iranian.org
Home/
About/HistoryMission & VisionFAQMedia Kit
Research/BooksPublicationsMyth vs. FactIndustry SpotlightMedia Guides
News/Iran NewsAIC NewsStatements
Media/Iran ChatVideo GalleryPhoto Gallery
Support/DonateInternshipsVolunteer
Contact/
American Iranian Council
CONTRIBUTE
Contact Us
Sign up for Newsletter
First Name
Last Name
Email Address
*
Zip Code
Thank you!
@AIC
AIC
RT @Michael_Lipin: .@AIC president @HAmirahmadi to @VOAIran on impending US sanctions against #Iran's FM Zarif: “He was stupid & naive… https://t.co/gGSvLCNaBc
Jun 28, 2019, 10:06 AM
AIC
AIC Statement on Escalating Tensions Between the United States and Iran https://t.co/LOix3w7OjM
Jun 15, 2019, 2:10 AM
AIC
AIC's newest Media Guide explores the reasons for, and ramifications of last month's designation of Iran's Revoluti… https://t.co/w2CTXFh0oa
May 17, 2019, 4:33 AM
© 2011-2016 American Iranian Council  | Home | Contact Us | Privacy Policy
